Guide to the Oliver F. Atkins photograph collection, 1943-1975
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Prints, 1943-1974; (48 boxes)
  - Subseries 1.2: Nixon White House Subject, 1968-1974, (23 boxes)
    - Trip To China, February 1972 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Trip To China, February 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Trip To China, February 1972 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Trip To China, February 1972 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Trip To China, February 1972 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Trip To China, February 1972 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Trip To Europe, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Trip To Europe, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Trip To Hawaii - Mrs. Nixon, 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Trip To Iceland - Pompidou, 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Trip To Mexico, 1969-1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Trip To Mideast, 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Trip To Mideast, 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Trip To Mideast, 1969-1974 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Trip To Pacific, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Trip To Russia, 1970-973 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Trip To Russia, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Trip To Russia, June 1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Trip To Russia, June 1972 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Trip To Russia, June 1972 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Trip To Russia, June 1972 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Trip To Russia, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Trip To Russia, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Trip to South America - Mrs. Nixon, March 1974 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Trip Around The World, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Trip Around The World, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Trip Around The World, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Urban Renewal, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Vietnam Peace Talks and POW Pictures, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Vice President Agnew, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Vice President Agnew, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Vice President Ford, 1969-1974 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - (Tricia's) Wedding, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - (Tricia's) Wedding, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - White House - Exteriors, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - White House - Exteriors, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - White House - Interiors, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - White House - Oval Office, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Women With The President, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Youth With President, 1969-1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 1.3: Nixon White House Chronological, 1968-1974, (10 boxes)
    Subseries 1.3 consists of both 8x10" and 11x14" prints arranged chronologically from Atkins' work as the personal photographer to President Richard M. Nixon. The prints cover much of the same subject matter as in Subseries 1.2 and in some cases are duplicates. Unlike Subseries 1.2, most of the prints are black and white.
    - Chronological, February 3-13, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, February 14-27, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, March 1-31, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, April 1-14, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, April 15-29, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, May 1-23, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, July 4-27, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, September 1968 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, October 1968 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, November 1968 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, January 20-31, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, July 28-31, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, August 1-27, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, September 6-28, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, December 4-31, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, January 3-31, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, February 19-March 16, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, April 10-29, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, May 9-29, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, June 3-30, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, July 1-21, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, July 22-29, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, August 1-28, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, September 16-28, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, October 5-13, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Chronological, October 14-24, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Chronological, October 25-28, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, October 29-30, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, October 31, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, November 1-11, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, December 1-30, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, January 1-13,1971 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, January 14-26, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, February 5-27, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, March 1-26, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, April 12-30, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, May 1-29, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, June 12-22, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, July 7-18, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, August 1-8, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, August 10-18, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, August 19-26, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, September 3-30, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, October 16-29. 1971 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, November 8-29, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, December 1-25, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, January 2-9, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, February 2-26, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, February 4-28, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, April 5-19, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, May 4-24, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, June 1, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, July 5-28, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, August 11, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, August 19-22, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, August 23-27, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, September 9-29, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, October 5-21, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, November 5-7, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, November 13-20, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, November 21, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, November 22-27, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, December 8, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, January 4-20, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, February 2-21, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, March 17-29, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, April 4-27, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, May 2-25, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, May 26-31, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, June 5-29, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Chronological, July 2-31, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Chronological, August 3-20, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Chronological, September 22, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Chronological, October 8-26, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Chronological, December 11-27, 1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, January 17-30, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Chronological, February 13,1974 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Chronological, March 12-30, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Chronological, April 19-29, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Chronological, May 30-31, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Chronological, June 2-27, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Chronological, June 28-30, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Chronological, July 1-3, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Chronological, July 8-28, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Chronological, August 7-8, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Chronological, August 9, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
      1 of 4; 1968 campaign
    - Undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
      2 of 4; 1968 campaign
    - Undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
      3 of 4; 1968 campaign
    - Undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
      4 of 4; 1968 campaign
- Series 2: 4x5" Negatives, 1947-1956; (9 boxes)
  Series 2 contains 4x5" negatives created during Atkins's tenure as a photographer for the Saturday Evening Post. Subjects include American political figures, such as Dwight D. Eisenhower, Alben W. Barkley, George Marshall, and Tom Connally; Washington, D.C., sites, such as the White House, the Library of Congress, and Howard University; and religious leaders, such as Ezra Taft Benson and Prophet Jones. Other subjects include American businessmen, military figures, and average citizens. Folder numbers refer to numbered "packets" containing multiple negatives of the same subject. Box 58 contains negatives other than 4x5" that could not be housed in the same containers. Some of these negatives are from the same stories and have the same packet numbering. Detailed caption descriptions for these packets can be found in Series 4. The dates following the titles refer to the story publication dates, and the dates in the scope notes refer to the dates that Atkins' took the photographs.
  - Your Garden is Their Business, April 9, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Ferry-Morse Seed Company, Detroit, Michigan, January 1955; 18 negatives
  - George Allen - When a President Needs Friend, May 5, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    March 1956; 9 negatives
    Also see Box 58
  - Fort Lauderdale - New Style in Florida Booms, February 18, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    December 1955; 34 negatives
  - Scientific Muscle Man, March 8, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Includes Winston Churchill and Harry S. Truman; 36 negatives
  - Tough Job for a Soldier, October 15, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Maxwell Taylor, August 1955; 14 negatives
  - The Secrets of Jamestown, February 9, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    Jamestown, Virginia, May 1956; 17 negatives
  - Boss of the Bindman, March 10, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Donald Quarles; 13 negatives
  - Ever Get Spots on Your Clothes, November 19, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    National Institute of Dry Cleaning; 19 negatives
  - Damndest Place in Washington, August 19, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    Library of Congress, June 1950; 25 negatives
  - We Remodeled Our House - And How!, July 28, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    Georgetown, Washington, D.C.; 23 negatives
  - They've Got the Facts on You, May 26, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    14 negatives
  - Clown on Capitol Hill, December 20, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    T. James Tumulty
  - How We Built Our School, June 16, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    12 negatives
  - Bats Are My Best Friend, February 4, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    Ernest P. Walker; 5 negatives
  - Are The Politicians Running The Veteran's Hospital?, October 4, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    Hines, Illinois, August 1950; 8 negatives
  - Desperate People at My Door, March 3, 1951 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    James Bryden; 9 negatives
  - The Multimillionaire Nobody Knows, May 5, 1951 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    Robert Woodruff, December 1950; 47 negatives
  - They Didn't Want That Guided Missile, September 3, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    July 1955; 26 negatives
  - Coal Miners - What They Say About John L. Lewis, December 28, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    37 negatives
  - Ike's Yankee Lieutenant, January 24, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    Sherman Adams, December 1952; 14 negatives
  - The Money Surgeons, July 4, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    May 1953; 18 negatives
  - Forrestal, Bradley, Vandenburg and Denfield, September 1948 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    James Forrestal, Hoyt Vandenburg, Omar Bradley, Louis Denfield; 18 negatives
  - The Hard Life of a New Congressman, November 17, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    Steven Derounian; 18 negatives
  - They Called Him Disabled, April 11, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    Charles Potter, November 1952; 17 negatives
  - Big Noise from Nebraska, August 5, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    Kenneth Wherry; 13 negatives
  - Can Senator Taft Win His Biggest Fight?, June 30, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    Robert Taft; 32 negatives
  - What's So Bad About a Professor's Job?, March 18, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    Arthur Whitehall; 13 negatives
  - Headaches of a Hotelkeeper - Part 2 and 3, December 14 and 21, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    Statler Hotel; 35 negatives
  - Mr. Truman's Mystery Man, December 24, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 33)
    David K. Niles
  - The Candid Congressman from Connecticut, June 21, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 34)
    Abraham Ribicoff; 2 negatives
  - Lindbergh, April 11, 1953 (Box 50, Folder 35)
    Spirit of St. Louis, Smithsonian Institution, March 1953; 8 negatives
  - What Would You Do with Triplets?, December 29, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 36)
    27 negatives
  - The Starling Nuisance, It's Driving Everybody Crazy, April 26, 1952 (Box 50, Folder 37)
    9 negatives
  - The Unsolved Riddle of the Oysters, November 10, 1951 (Box 50, Folder 38)
    Milford, Connecticut, September 1951; 16 negatives
  - That Man Junior, September 24, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 39)
    Includes Franklin D. Roosevelt, Jr, John F. Kennedy, Robert Blaikie, Alex Rose; 10 negatives
  - The Man Who Stops Fights, August 13, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 40)
    Ralph Bunche; 10 negatives
  - Bat and Butterfly Test - Why Animals Don't Need Map, October 1, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 41)
    June 1955; 7 negatives
  - Secret Tricks of the Sea, June 23, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 42)
    Atlantic City, New Jersey, 1955; 22 negatives
  - Mystery Man of the White House, February 6, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 43)
    Robert Cutler; 13 negatives
  - The Legend of Stephen Foster, February 6, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 44)
    Stephen Foster, January 1953; 11 negatives
  - The GIs Who Fell for the Reds, March 6, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 45)
    James Pinkston; 8 negatives
  - Watch Your Step at the Conventions!, June 5, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 46)
    5 negatives
  - Mr. Truman's Glamor Boy, June 4, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    Maurice Tobin; 29 negatives
  - How to be a Crime Buster, March 19, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    Warren Olney III; 5 negatives
  - Battle of Giants in Kentucky, September 18, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 48a)
    17 negatives
  - Paratrooper in the Pentagon, August 28, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    James Maurice Gavin; 29 negatives
  - The Case for Federal Relief, June 19, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 51)
    April 1952; 33 negatives
  - My Three Years as a Dead Man (6 parts), January 23 to February 27, 1954 (Box 51, Folder 52)
    William F. Dean; 13 negatives
  - He Exposed the Thefts in the Revenue Bureau, March 1, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 54)
    John J. Williams; 22 negatives
  - The Truth About General Grow's Moscow Diary, September 27, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - We're Licking the Terror of the Arctic, August 16, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 57)
    June 1952; 17 negatives
  - How Not to Get Seasick, July 11, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 59)
    May 1953; 32 negatives
  - The Senate's Big Brain, July 4, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 60)
    Eugene Millikin, April 1953; 23 negatives
  - The Woes of Washington, August 1, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 61)
    8 negatives
  - The Old School Bus Comes Adventuring, July 29, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 62)
    May 1950; 4 negatives
  - Tom Connally - The Senator Loves a Fight, July 1, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 63)
    Tom Connally, includes Harry S. Truman; 30 negatives
  - Your Money May Soon Cost Less, April 19, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 64)
    4 negatives
  - We Flew the Atlantic in Helicopters, November 1, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 65)
    13 negatives
  - They Don't Want Uncle's Money, March 22, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 66)
    February 1952; 20 negatives
  - Baseball's Improbable Imports, August 2, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 67)
    Washington Senators baseball team; 14 negatives
  - Elder Benson's Going to Catch It, March 28, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 68)
    Ezra Taft Benson, February 1953; 9 negatives
  - Just What the Doctor Ordered, July 22, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 69)
    December 1949; 20 negatives
  - I Was There, February 25, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 70)
    William Leahy; 14 negatives
  - Are We Letting Our Children Down?, May 13, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 71)
    April 1950; 30 negatives
  - Uncle Sam's Strange Filing Case, April 24, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 72)
    National Archives and Records Administration, June 1948; 30 negatives
  - Portrait of a Union Boss, February 28, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 73)
    George Tetlet, December 1947; 32 negatives
  - Rebel in Illinois, April 2, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 74)
    Adlai Stevenson, Springfield and Bloomfield, Illinois, February 1949; 31 negatives
  - The CEO's Political Hot Shot, February 1949 (Box 52, Folder 75)
    Jack Kroll; 19 negatives
  - Ike's Depression Doctor, April 17, 1954 (Box 52, Folder 79)
    Arthur Burns, includes Dwight D. Eisenhower; 10 negatives
  - Too Much Is Our Trouble - Wheat Storage on Ships in Hudson River, June 18, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 81A)
    23 negatives
  - White House under Construction, undated (Box 52, Folder 81B)
  - Admiral Halsey Tells His Story, June 14 to August 9, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 82)
    William F. Halsey, USS Missouri; 4 color positives
  - Beverly Smith, undated (Box 52, Folder 83)
  - Ferenc Nagy, Prime Minister of Hungary, June 1947 (Box 52, Folder 84)
  - Prophet Jones, Messiah in Mink, March 5, 1955 (Box 52, Folder 85)
    James Francis Marion Jones; 59 negatives
  - Stormy New Boss of the Pentagon, July 30, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 86)
    Louis Arthur Johnson, June 1949; 5 negatives
  - Washington's Flossiest Hotel, February 11, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 87)
    Carlton hotel, Washington, D.C., August 1949; 3 negatives
  - They Teach Trains to Whistle, April 29, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 88)
    March 1950; 1 negative
  - Norway's Democratic Diplomat, undated (Box 53, Folder 89)
    Wilhelm Munthe. de Morgenstierne; 12 negatives
  - Man Hunt, September 30, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 91)
    Clifford Garner, July 1950; 9 negatives
  - The Rebellious Parson, February 10, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 92)
    Library of Congress, July 1950; 9 negatives
  - The Man Who Looks Like Truman, February 17, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 93)
    Irving Fisher; 29 negatives
  - Lightning Joe, the GI's General, January 27, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 94)
    Joseph Lawton Collins, November 1950; 8 negatives
  - Smartest Dog in Maryland, November 11, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 95)
    H. K. Riggs; 9 negatives
  - Senator Douglas: Hard-Boiled Idealist, August 6, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 96)
    Paul Douglas; 17 negatives
  - The Army's Most Hysterical Post, December 18, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 100)
    35 negatives
  - The Fighting Half-Pint of Capitol Hill, June 18, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 101)
    Frank P. Graham, includes Kerr Scott, May 1949; 22 negatives
  - Washington's Greatest Story Teller, July 2, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 102)
    Alben W. Barkley, includes Harry F. Byrd; 18 negatives
  - Man's Best Friend is a Shovel, June 12, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 103)
    June 1952; 5 negatives
  - How Washington's Color Line Looks to me, April 3, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 104)
    February 1954; 5 negatives
  - They're Revealing The World's Oldest Secret, March 14, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 105)
    September 1952; 12 negatives
  - How My Hired Man Handles Me, June 20, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 106)
    Jim Perry, Bud Camp; 25 negatives
  - My Customers Get Garden Fever Every Spring, March 21, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 107)
    Milo Coplan; October and November 1952; 31 negatives
  - How Europe's Defenses Look to Me, October 10, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 108)
    Matthew B. Ridgway; 13 negatives
  - League of Frightened Women, October 23, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 110)
    League of Women Voters; 18 negatives
  - Pied Pipers of Ice Cream, August 20, 1949 (Box 53, Folder 111)
    Good Humor Corporation, April 1949; 39 negatives
  - The Toughest Job Facing Ike, March 14, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 112)
    William M. Fechteler, Omar Bradley, Hoyt Vandenberg, J. Lawton Collins; 14 negatives, 1 color positive
  - Their Last World Had a Punch, April 17, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 113)
    Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, February 1954; 2 negatives
  - Uncle Sam's Favorite Trouble Shooter, June 26, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 114)
    Robert Murphy; 12 negatives
  - I Should Have Died, September 4, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 115)
    Albert Roth, includes Richard M. Nixon, June 1954; 19 negatives
  - Secretary of State George Marshall, October 1950 (Box 53, Folder 117)
    Includes Dean Acheson; 9 negatives
  - This School is Ready for the H-Bomb, September 25, 1954 (Box 54, Folder 118)
    39 negatives
  - Congress Puts This Show on the Road, February 14, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 119)
    Mike Monroney, Charles B. Brownson; 13 negatives
  - We Found Lincoln's Last Bank Account, February 14, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 120)
    November 1952; 21 negatives
  - What Are You Getting for Your $12,000,000,000, December 5, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 121)
    Atomic Energy Commission; September 1953; 18 negatives
  - He Followed Mom to Congress, August 15, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 122)
    Frances P. Bolton, Oliver P. Bolton, June 1953; 13 negatives
  - Congress vs. the Plunging Neckline, December 27, 1952 (Box 54, Folder 123)
    Mrs. Winfield Smart, November 1952; 5 negatives
  - Charlotte, North Carolina, June 23, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 126)
    34 negatives
  - The President's Day, December 1953 (Box 54, Folder 127)
    Dwight D. Eisenhower; 42 negatives
  - Little Angels of Phelps Place, August 1953 (Box 54, Folder 128)
    21 negatives
  - Korean POW Story, November 1953 (Box 54, Folder 129)
    Ray "Mike" Dow; 22 negatives
  - I Rode Uncle Sam's Gravy Train, October 1953 (Box 54, Folder 130)
    Tom Durrance; 15 negatives
  - How Our Foreign Policy Is Made, March 1949 (Box 54, Folder 131)
    Sidney W. Souers, includes Dean Acheson; 15 negatives
  - I Saved The Panama Canal, April 23, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 132)
    Josephine Crisler, October 1948; 10 negatives
  - The Marine Corps Fights for Its Life, February 5, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 133)
    Clifton Bledsoe Cates; December 1948; 10 negatives
  - America's Leading Negro University, February 19, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 134)
    Howard University, November 1948; 24 negatives
  - First Florist of the Land, September 10, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 135)
    Robert M. Redmond, August 1949; 5 negatives
  - Robert L. Eichelberger, February 1949 (Box 54, Folder 136A)
    16 negatives
  - We Try to Make It Easy for You, February 21, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 136B)
    George J. Schoeneman; 1 negative
  - J. Willard Marriott, September 1948 (Box 54, Folder 137)
    38 negatives
  - Lowell Mason, April 1948 (Box 55, Folder 138)
  - Hoyt Vandenberg, June 1948 (Box 55, Folder 139)
    24 negatives
  - Dewey Train, undated (Box 55, Folder 141)
    1 negatives
  - Stacy Jones, February 1949 (Box 55, Folder 142)
  - Jugs, Bugs and Airpower, January 1949 (Box 55, Folder 143)
    B-29s, Tucson Arizona; 41 negatives
  - I Prowled Russia's Forbidden Zone, December 11, 1948 to January 1, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 144)
    Werner Knop, October 1948; 12 negatives
  - They're Just Wild about Boudreau, September 4, 1948 (Box 55, Folder 145)
    Lou Boudreau, August 1948; 14 negatives
  - White House mail room, September 1948 (Box 55, Folder 146)
  - House of Music Has The Power to Heal, June 24, 1946 (Box 55, Folder 148)
    40 negatives
  - Voice of America, August 1947 (Box 55, Folder 149)
    45 negatives
  - Fifth Army artillery unit, undated (Box 55, Folder 150)
    Witton Lawler; 6 negatives
  - Postman in the Cabinet, January 24, 1948 (Box 55, Folder 153)
    Jesse M. Donaldson, December 1947; 21 negatives
  - Washington Five Percenters, August 1949 (Box 55, Folder 154)
    Paul Brindle, Alden H. Waite, Clyde R. Hoey, Herbert Feldman, Harry Vaughn, John F. Maragon; 77 negatives
  - America's Leading Negro University, February 19, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 155)
    Howard University, December 1948; 26 negatives
  - James Forrestal, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 156)
    1 negative
  - Christian Herter, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 157)
    22 negatives
  - Clark Clifford, August 1947 (Box 56, Folder 158)
    15 negatives